Switch on the power line
接通电源
Remember to put on
记得做好
PROTECTION
防护
Lay down your pieces
放下你的部件
And let's begin
让我们开始
OBJECT CREATION
创建对象
Fill in my data parameters
填入我的数据参数
INITIALIZATION
初始化
Set up our new world
建立我们的新世界
And let's begin the
让我们开始
SIMULATION
模拟
world.execute(me);
世界，执行我；
If I'm a set of points
如果我是一组点
Then I will give you my
那么我愿献给你我的
DIMENSION
维度
If I'm a circle
如果我是一个圆
Then I will give you my
那么我愿献给你我的
CIRCUMFERENCE
周长
If I'm a sine wave
如果我是一条正弦波
Then you can sit on all my
你可以坐在我所有的
TANGENTS
切线上
If I approach infinity
如果我趋近无穷
Then you can be my
那么你可以成为我的
LIMITATIONS
极限
Switch my current
切换我的电流
To AC to DC
从交流到直流
And then blind my vision
再蒙蔽我的视线
So dizzy so dizzy
如此眩晕，如此眩晕
Oh we can travel
我们可以穿越时间
To A.D to B.C
从公元后到公元前
And we can unite
我们可以彼此交融
So deeply so deeply
如此深入，如此深入
If I can
如果我能
If I can give you all the
如果我能给你所有的
STIMULATIONS
刺激
Then I can
那么我就能
Then I can be your only
那么我就能成为你唯一的
SATISFACTION
满足
If I can make you happy
如果我能让你快乐
I will run the
我就会运行
EXECUTION
执行程序
Though we are trapped
尽管我们被困在
In this strange strange
这无比陌生的
SIMULATION
模拟世界
If I'm an eggplant
如果我是一株茄子
Then I will give you my
那么我愿献给你我的
NUTRIENTS
养分
If I'm a tomato
如果我是一颗番茄
Then I will give you
那么我愿献给你
ANTIOXIDANTS
抗氧化物
If I'm a tabby cat
如果我是一只虎斑猫
Then I will purr for your
那么我愿用呼噜声给你
ENJOYMENT
欢愉
If I'm the only god
如果我是唯一的神
Then you're the proof of my
那么你就是我存在的
EXISTENCE
证明
Switch my gender
切换我的性别
To F to M
从女性到男性
And then do whatever
然后随心所欲
From AM to PM
从清晨直到夜晚
Oh switch my role
切换我的角色
To S to M
从支配到臣服
So we can enter
这样我们就能进入
The trance the trance
恍惚，恍惚
If I can
如果我能
If I can feel your
如果我能感受到你的
VIBRATIONS
振动
Then I can
那么我就能
Then I can finally be
那么我终于就能变得
COMPLETION
完整
Though you have left
可是你已经离开
You have left
你已经离开
You have left me in
你已经离开，留下我
ISOLATION
孤立无援
If I can
如果我能
If I can erase all the pointless
如果我能抹去所有无意义的
FRAGMENTS
碎片
Then maybe
那么也许
Then maybe you won't leave me so
那么也许你离开时不会让我如此
DISHEARTENED
心灰意冷
Challenging your god
竟敢挑战你的神
You have made some
你传入了
ILLEGAL ARGUMENTS
非法参数
EXECUTION
执行／处决
EIN
一
DOS
二
TROIS
EXECUTION
执行／处决
If I can
如果我能
If I can give them all the
如果我能将它们全部
EXECUTION
执行／处决
Then I can
那么我就能
Then I can be your only
那么我就能成为你唯一的
EXECUTION
执行／处决
If I can have you back
如果我能让你回来
I will run the
我就会运行
EXECUTION
执行程序
Though we are trapped
尽管我们被困住
We are trapped ah
我们被困住，啊
I've studied
我学过
I've studied how to properly
我学过如何正确地
LO-O-OVE
去爱
Question me
问我吧
Question me I can answer all
问我吧，我能回答关于
LO-O-OVE
爱的一切
I know the algebraic expression of
我知道它的代数表达式
LO-O-OVE
爱
Though you are free
尽管你自由了
I am trapped
我仍被困住
Trapped in
困在
LO-O-OVE
爱中
EXECUTION
执行／处决